Spirit Club Hall
Spirit Club Hall?
Do you know them?
I've heard about them,
but I didn't know there's one here.
We don't seek publicity.
Without looking for it,
a club hall is normally unknown.
This is your card.
And this is from Laozi.
For me?
It helps with recovery.
Thank you.
Do I bring it back when I used it up?
Not necessary.
You can use it up to a considerable amount.
Did Laozi tell you anything?
No, he didn't.
This card is also a pass to every club hall.
We offer services for all spirits who visit us.
For everyone?
You aren't aware of how club halls work today.
Shall I expain it to you?
Do you have time?
Of course, it's part of my job.
Spirit Club Halls were founded by Laozi and two other deities.
There's one in each large human city.
They offer services for spirits.
Besides acting as an inn, like in old times,
it also provides financial support for living in the human world.
And what's to do for it?
Nothing.
You only have to keep the rules of the hall.
What are the rules?
Don't slay your own kind.
Don't reveal yourself in front of humans.
If you're willing to be summoned by us,
you can get even more benefits.
So are you gonna fight today, or not?!
Come on!
All right, I'll keep my mouth shut!
This is our practice field.
They're the ones we just met.
They are frequent visitors.
They can't live in the city because of their appearance.
Are they strong spirits?
Yes.
Then how come they can't take a human form?
All spirits have their genuine form.
It's not about cultivation.
A human form is good only for blending in.
Even those who can't transform can find an expert.
They simply think it's below them to look human.
I see...
And who is the strongest among them and you?
I must be the weakest here.
Then how come you're the hall manager?
I can make money.
How do you make money?
I sell these trees.
The lush vegetation here is your work, right?
Thank you.
Yes.
Trees born quickly from magic also die quickly.
But the trees whose growth I stimulate,
are capable of surviving.
Are trees that expensive?
Good wood is extremely valuable.
Especially nowadays.
And moneymaking made you the boss?
Of course not.
Let's go a floor up.
There's one more floor?
Stand still.
This is the core of the hall.
You can see the location and data of every club hall.
It's quite spectacular.
It's better at places with bigger bandwidth.
Space fluctuations...
This isn't just a map, is it?
It's much more.
Every dot on the map represents a club hall.
Beside being a sign,
each dot actually connects us to a hall.
You say these are all space points?
Yes.
This is really awesome.
Mr. Qianzhen.
Hey, Manager!
Showing them around?
The others are waiting.
You should hurry.
See ya later, little spirits!
Some people have a meet-up here.
He doesn't hate humans?
He can't tell who's human.
Anyone can use this place?
Yes.
Aren't there troublemakers?
Not for a long time.
You can see there our club hall.
The color of the upper dot shows the profile of the hall.
Ours is gold, as we do mainly commerce.
The dots below stand for the resident spirits.
There's three of us here, including Tu Bei and me.
But also human assistants work in every hall.
And how do they offer support
at halls which don't do commerce?
Resources are shared among halls.
Like capital, space, military force,
magic weapons and tools.
The hall manager can use them within his authority.
If there are people even here,
why is it a rule that you can't reveal yourself to humans?
In fact, many people know about our existence.
Like you, a confidant of Lord Xuanli.
But not every human can tolerate us.
It was better back then,
but since people got stronger, we've got troubles.
After a few incidents, we established the current rules.
This is the best way now to get along.
I don't really get it...
Why do you have to earn money in the first place?
Can't you just create gold or money?
It would wreck up the human financial world.
On the long run, it's best to do commerce following their rules.
That means I should open an ice warehouse.
I will steal.
That's not "making" money...
Or you could do express deliveries.
Why not?
That was the introduction.
Would you like to hear some more details?
Not for now.
Let us have a cup of tea.
Won't you stay for lunch?
Sorry, my grandfather is waiting for me.
Today we can't.
It's all right.
This is for you.
For me?
Feel free to accept it.
It's from Laozi.
Didn't you promise anime merch to him?
Oh...
Should I take you to Shan Xin's?
We're going to an anime con tomorrow.
I'll go home and renovate the shrine.
See you the day after tomorrow.
Hello!
Shan Xin!
How did you know I'm here?
Yeah, I was about to visit you.
Out there?!
'Sup, Gen.
Why are you here...?
I came for Xiaobai.
And Xiaohei, for Huang.
I'd rather go home...
What's wrong?
Mr. Fu and co. have left.
They went to the city.
They know how to behave.
They might be following Lord Xuanli.
Get off.
Unless you want to be attacked on the bus.
What can I do for you?
Let's do some sparring.
What are we doing here?
Conflict means chance.
What if they find us?
Someone's here.
What do we do?
Can we say we just passed here?
We can't.
What are you doing here?
We came to help you!
He won't buy this...
Silence.
Dongdong
Bobo
Mang Yan
Gen
Kali
Mutou
Yunfei
Da Shuang
Service staff:
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Hu Niu
Kucha
Dandan
Fenmo
Biti Chaogan ZC
Gen, Xiaobai, Xiaohei:
Shan Xin
Tu Bei:
Baomu Zhongyang
Kali:
Xiahou Luofeng
Qingqiu:
Teng Xin
Fu:
Tutehameng
He still
hasn't spoken yet
↘
Sound engineer:
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sun Yujing
Sun Zhongyang
Wang Miao
Bohe
They're having fun.
Not both of them.
They are equally strong.
What do you think, Polao?
One is just brute force.
The other is weak and powerless.
Who do you mean, you old geezer?
You and him.
Shut up, silly old frog!
This is bad...
Axian.
Let's go!
Don't cut me down...
Why are you in such a hurry?
He cut the space switch.
'Return home'?
It launches slowly.
Stay alert.
If there's no more business,
may I leave now?
We came for the Sky Pearl.
Are you willing to part with it?
Just as I thought.
What do you mean?
The prizes of vow quests can be robbed.
I suppose you knew about this.
You get the wrong idea.
You say the Sky Pearl you have is not from Laozi?
I don't have any Sky Pearl.
Oh, no...
What's wrong?
He really doesn't have the Pearl.
So even you can be wrong?
Then it must be at the girl or the cat, surprisingly.
I was careless.
So may I leave now?
You shall keep our company for a few days.
You really get it wrong.
I can tell truth and lies apart.
It's useless to try to deny.
If you want to leave, you must defeat all of us.
Darn...
We won't bother you any longer...
You don't bother us.
We have to trouble you for a while.
Mission: Sky Pearl
Xiaobai!
Go forward and throw a grenade!
Sure!
Kitty Grenade
Xiaobai!
Are you all right?
Milk
See you out there.
Settings
Exit
What do you say?
You're awesome!
Isn't this available only since yesterday?
It's nothing.
I'm a pro after all.
I'm so tired...
What does it say?
Can I eat it?
This spirit space is quite comfortable.
Aren't you worried?
Why would I be?
For your comrades.
It makes no sense to worry.
I can't do anything.
But last time you beat us hard.
Because you guys are weak.
Oh.
Why is there a wall here?
Axian!
The space ends here!
It ends abruptly?
It doesn't help us.
Aren't spirit spaces spherical?
Only natural, complete spaces are.
Really?
Since we're together in trouble now,
will you tell me now why you came here?
'River Fu' Spirit Elixir.
The day after a stable state is reached,
take one pill in the morning,
during the day and at the evening,
and you are cured.
Postscript!
Say hello to Wuxian for me.
This is written here.
I see.
Are you talking to Xiaohei?
Yeah.
Keep on dreaming, girl...
Xiaohei can understand me.
And Xiaohuang understands me.
Huang!
Why are you so silly now?
And can he understand a lot?
Be happy!
Smile!
Say meow!
Convinced yet?
Can't see the difference.
It's easy.
Be happy!
Be scared!
Convinced yet?
I'm telling the truth.
Not only he can understand me,
but I can understand him too.
How is this possible?
Xiaobai.
You can tell her that we can communicate,
but don't talk about spirits.
Okay.
What if it's true...?
I need to test it.
We're going to an anime con tomorrow.
Xiaobai is the cutest.
Oh, please, don't flatter me!
This is awesome!
One more test!
You took Xiaohei to the bathroom,
but just stared at him and didn't say a word.
Believe it now?
I believe it.
Xiaohei also understands Piyu.
He can translate for me.
Huang, you're useless.
Xiaohei says Xiaohuang says he's hungry.
You little glutton...
Dinner's ready!
Got it, you're awesome.
Coming!
Musi, Axian and Tanjiu.
So you three came for the Sky Pearl too?
Are you mad at us, Lord Xuanli?
Not at all.
This might be your lucky day.
You need it for cultivation?
Yes.
Spirit force is scarce today.
Cultivation got much harder.
Sorry we left you alone.
Have you found it?
For the time being, no.
It's hard to trace those riding a vehicle.
You said earlier that if we can find it,
you give it to us, am I right?
Of course.
We've got no chance against you.
And I want them to be safe.
We appreciate it.
How can a robbery be that civilized?
They are all well-mannered.
Just now...
I thought I've heard you call him Xuanli.
Is it a problem?
No.
But he is not Xuanli.
I never said I was him.
Directed by:
Mutou
Kali
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Bobo
Dongdong
Animation:
Meat Mountain (Rou Shan)
Cool Tiger (Shuai Hu)
Leaf (Yezi)
Mouse (Haozi)
Cooing Pigeon (Jiu Jiu)
Wen Tao
Pomelo (Youzi)
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Qi Feng
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Character design:
Snot (Biti)
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Service staff:
Huniu
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Kucha
Xiaobai, Shan Xin,
Xiaohei, Xiaohuang, Gen:
Shan Xin
Musi, Axian, Tanjiu:
Ding Dang
Qingqiu,
Qianzhen:
Teng Xin
Fu, Polao:
Tutehameng
Sound engineer:
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Xu Wei
Bohe
Wang Miao
Wow!
So many people!
Well, yeah.
It's the biggest anime convention in town.
I didn't know Xiaohei was interested in this.
It's rare for a cat.
I didn't want to stay there...
Directed by:
Mutou
Character design:
Biti
Key animation:
Gen
Kali
Bobo
Dongdong
Animation:
Rou Shan
Shuai Hu
Yezi
Haozi
Jiu Jiu
Wen Tao
Youzi
October (Shiyue)
Backgrounds:
Mang Yan
Qi Feng
Cat Dregs (Mao Zha)
Modeling:
Da Shuang
Lulu
Big Yellow (Da Huang)
Sunflower Paper (Kui Zhi)
Design:
Fenmo
Dandan
Service staff:
Hu Niu
Tu Bei
Tu Yi
Kucha
Xiaobai, Shan Xin
Xiaohei, Xiaohuang, Gen:
Shan Xin
Diting:
Huang Zhenji
Congratulations on your wedding!
Dom Shan took Sub Huang captive
Qingqiu,
Qianzhen:
Teng Xin
Fu, Polao:
Tutehameng
Why are we all crammed here?
Musi, Axian, Tanjiu:
Ding Dang
Bear with it, there's
a wedding over there
Crowd:
Youwu Yueshan
Li Lanling
Mutou
The newlyweds
Sound engineer:
Piyu:
Tao Bao
Heishu:
Ai Suo
Sound:
Sun Yujing
Sun Zhongyang
Bohe
Wang Miao
Anime Convention
I've sensed them.
This one, please.
Thanks for your purchase!
What did you buy?
Just a small gift.
Xiaobai?
Handsome guy.
"Gate of the Living" is now available at Sector B3.
An ID is required to make a purchase.
Do not use another person's name.
I'll go stand in line.
You go have fun.
I'll go with you.
You won't buy that.
We'll meet when I'm done.
I don't want you to go alone.
It's okay, Dad's here.
Hello, Mr. Shan!
I'm going now.
I'll call you.
Okay.
Feeling better, kitten?
Much better.
Why didn't you come back to the tower last time?
Leave the past alone...
What's the topic?
World politics.
What brings you here?
Shopping for Master Lao.
I want to do that too.
What a coincidence that we meet here!
I've heard your voice, so I came here.
You come here often?
Yes.
I can be myself here.
You like conventions?
Hi, can we make some pictures with you?
Sure.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Who does he cosplay?
No idea, but he's so cute!
Oho...
You're yourself, huh?
Exactly.
I don't have to disguise myself here.
So it was Tanjiu who created your copies.
Only your spirit parts are here right now?
Yes.
Our real bodies are in a safe place.
We won't get hurt even if our copies are destroyed.
Of course, if we don't get them back,
we lose cultivation.
Judging by your appearance,
I assume you live among humans, right?
Yes.
We even have jobs.
You do?
We are...
comic book artists!
Comic book
artists
They're late
with manuscripts
on cultivation days
I've never met a spirit who has such a job.
So you are in fact not Lord Xuanli?
That's right.
May I ask your family name?
Luo.
Wolverine?
Never mind...
Will we stay here forever?
Of course not.
I suppose you'd rather leave too.
So you have a plan.
If we join forces,
we can't defeat them,
but it's easy to escape.
These here?
Will he like them?
We'd like these two, please.
Right away.
By the way...
Can you take this to Laozi?
You bought it for him?
Why don't you take it yourself?
I wanted to.
But Gen said the Blue Jade Disc can be used only once in a month.
Then I'll take it to him.
Isn't it Laozi's personal magic tool?
How come it can't be used more often?
The Disc is a first-rate magic tool for fixed-point teleportation.
I suppose the limit was set especially for you.
But why?
He doesn't want me to visit more often?
I cannot tell.
You should ask him next time.
Okay.
Your badges are packed.
This is it?
Yes.
It's quite crowded...
It won't be easy...
So what now?
Wait until they come out?
Have you found it?
Yes.
It's time you kept your promise.
Don't you think it's strange you can't see those three?
Why do you say that?
So your closed eyes are just a facade.
I thought you rely on spirit sense.
Haven't you noticed they already left?
None of you can leave this spirit space.
Don't be so sure about it.
None of you are space type.
How do you know we can't leave?
Qiuxian.
Stay here and watch.
I call Polao in.
So, what are all these humans doing here?
It's market day.
Polao.
Please come in for a minute.
They are not here.
Impossible.
They don't have such abilities.
Otherwise, why would they have stayed for so long?
They are going to look for the Sky Pearl.
Let's go.
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
Our destination may be whimsical
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
kore kara deau kimi e to
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Mochiyotta hako aketara
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Are so precious and so fleeting
Omoi wa kitto kienai
Those feelings will never fade away
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me